http://attra.ncat.org/privacy-policy/

ATTRA's COVID-19 statement
Update: You can now download any of our technical materials for FREE! See our full list of publications.
Privacy Policy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for ATTRA, a national sustainable agriculture assistance program managed by the National Center for Appropriate Technology (NCAT) and this website, www.attra.org. We are committed to maintaining the privacy of our visitors and donors and below you will learn about information we collect, with whom it is shared, how it can be corrected, and how it is secured.
Information Collection, Use and Sharing
We collect the IP address, domain name and geographic location, but not the e-mail address, of visitors to our Web site. We collect name, address, and email information for all credit card transactions. In addition, we collect aggregate usage information on numbers of individuals visiting pages and length of viewing pages. The information collected may be used to improve the content of our Web site. Visitor addresses will not be shared with other organizations or used for commercial purposes.
We do not sell, rent, give or lend personal information about our site visitors, donors, and/or clients to any advertisers or any other third party. We disclose personal information only to the extent necessary to respond to your information or donation request. For instance, if you submit a question to us, the experts responding to your query will be better able to respond if they know your location and the activity in which you are involved. Plus, they need to know how to contact you with the reply to your question.
Choice/Opt Out
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site also provides users options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications.
1. You can send an email to: 4info@ncat.org
2. You can call 800-275-6228
3. You can click on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of each of our official email communications.
Correct/Update
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.
1. You can send an email to: 4info@ncat.org
2. You can call 800-275-6228
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information you provide. Your data is password protected to guard against unauthorized access. In addition, all data moving between our website and your browser is encrypted using SSL, the strongest available protection on the internet.
Google Analytics Demographics and Interests
NCAT uses Google Analytics demographics and interest reporting to collect information on our web visitors such as age, gender and interests. We use this information to help guide our website content as well as marketing and communications efforts.
Links
This Web site is linked to many other sites. Please be aware that as you leave our Web site in following those links, the privacy policy and data collection practices of those other Web sites apply.
Disclaimer
Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, or guarantee it will always be secure from unauthorized access. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time and notify the public by notice posted on the website. If you have questions about this privacy statement, the practices of our website, or your dealings with the website, you can email or call using the information listed above, or complete the “Contact Us” form on this website.
Our contact information:
